Guide to the David Newton Henderson Papers, 1930-1976 RL.00528
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series
  - Ways and Means, 1961-March, 1962 (Box 425)
    1965-1966: legislation to federalize the unemployment compensation program; 1967: Social Security legislation; 1968: proposed reductions in non-military spending; 1970: tax reform, Social Security; 1971: welfare reform, national health care system, revenue sharing, Social Security; 1972: Tax Policy Review Bill, federal assistance to private schools; 1973: Pension Reform Bill, Trade Reform Act; 1974: tax exemption for small savings accounts, revenue sharing; 1975: tax reform, Roll-Over Pension Plan (ERISA); see also Social Security, Welfare, Welfare Reform
  - Ways and Means, April, 1962-May, 1965 (Box 426)
  - Ways and Means, June, 1965-1967 (Box 427)
  - Ways and Means, 1968-Sept., 1969 (Box 428)
  - Ways and Means, Oct., 1969-1970 (Box 429)
  - Ways and Means, 1971-1972 (Box 430)
  - Ways and Means, 1973 (Box 431)
  - Ways and Means, 1974-August, 1975 (Box 432)
  - Ways and Means, Sept.-Dec., 1975 (Box 433)
  - Welfare, 1961-1972See also Ways and Means (Box 433)
  - Welfare Reform, 1971 see also Ways and Means (Box 433)
  - Western Union, 1962 (Box 433)
  - White House, 1964-1968 (Box 433)
  - White House, 1970-1976 (Box 434)
  - Yarmolinski Affair, 1964-1965 (Box 435)
  - Yarmolinski Affair, 1964-1965 (cont.) (Box 435)
    In 1964 journalists charged that several Southern congressmen--particularly the North Carolina delegation--made the votes for the president's economic opportunity program contingent on the expulsion of Adam Yarmolinski from the administration of the program. These congressmen reportedly suspected Yarmolinski, a Jewish liberal of Russian descent, of subversion.
  - Young Democratic Club, 1962 (Box 435)
  - Miscellany, 1960-1963 (Box 435)
  - Miscellany, 1964-1967 (Box 436)
  - Miscellany, 1968-1970 (Box 437)
  - Miscellany, 1971-1976 (Box 438)
  - Postal Reorganization Comparative Print of H. R. 17070 as passed by the House and as Amended by the Senate. Committee Print No. 1, July 13, 1970 (Oversize-box 1)